# HAFIZ DALIMUNTHE S.E



## CONTACT

- **1** 087895122704
- hafizdalimunthe4@gmail.com
- JI.psr 3 no 33 A glugur darat I medan timur

### PROFILE

I am a bechelor of economic having 1 year more experience in some professional works. I am very experienced for admin, marketing and cashier. I am used to use microsoft office mainly excel vlookup, hlookup program and etc. I can speak english well with proving score TOEFL ITP 577. With entire my experiences and skills which i have i am ready for continuing my carrier as professional worker.

# SKILLS

- Problem solving
- Team work
- Interpersonal
- · adaptive
- Leadership
- Communication
- Time management

### EXPERIENCE

#### ADMIN MARKETING

#### PT Polo viena luggage

Feb 2021 - Dec 2021

- Data entry
- · Making schedule for employees
- · Diary management and arrangging appointments
- · Arranging both internal and external company

#### **ADMIN INTERN**

#### PT Nissan motors company

Feb 2019- April 2019

- Providing administration support to sales schedule
- Entry data new vehiche to release for costumers
- · Dealing with email enquiries
- · Making schedule for employees

#### ADMIN AND CASHIER

#### Roemah akmal cafe

2017-2018

- · Providing paid by costumers
- · Inputing monthly data report
- Writing income and expanditure company monthly

# EDUCATION

# BACHELOR OF ISLAMIC ECONOMIC UINSU MEDAN

2016-2020

# SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL 29 JAKARTA

2012-2015